# KISHAN

### **CONTACT INFO**

- (+91) 7359227564
- kaumik1219@gmail.com
- patelsaheb.com

# Mississauga, ONTARIO, CANADA

# **SOFTWARE ENGINEER**

### **PROFILE**

I have spent the past three years developing my skills so I can curate what I imagine as a reality. If you have a dream to create a digital system, I can be your go-to guy to make it a reality. I love sitting on my computer under a tree in my garden and code. If you don't find me on the computer, I would be either taking care of plants in the garden or hiking or taking a nap.

### **SKILLS**

React.js

Node.js

**React Native** 

**Firebase** 

Parse server

# **PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES**

JavaScript (ES6)

Python

Java

C ++

C

Arduino

# **LANGUAGES**

**English** 

Hindi

Gujarati

# **EXPERIENCE**

# **Full-Stack Developer**

Code Symphony LLP | September 2019 - March 2021

Here, I am developing multiple projects and sharpening my skills which I leanrned in past 3 years while learning new skills like time management, team cordination, client communication, etc.

# **Professional Freelancer**

Full Stack Engineer | January 2019 - August 2019

I was responsible for understanding requirements and managing a team of 2-3 developers while working on multiple projects. I learned skill like Reactjs, Express.js, Nodejs, React Native, MongoDB, Stripe, Parse Server

### **Itlion Software Services**

Software Developer Intern | June 2018 - December 2018

I was responsible for maintaining and developing an admin web app for their various CRM projects. I learned skills like javascript, Node-red, complex MongoDB queries, work as a team in startup culture.

### **Education**

# **Lambton College In Mississauga**

PG in Computer Software & Database Development | January 2021 - Present

# **Government Engineering College, Modasa**

Bachelors' Computer Engineering | June 2015 - May 2019

# Jawahar Navodaya Vidhyalaya, Kathlal

SSC and HSC | 2008-2015